<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CarsUSB</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">You don\'t have internet connection. Please check your internet and try again.</string>


    <!--login page deatils-->

    <string name="dealer_ID">dealer_ID</string>
    <string name="dealer_password">dealer_password</string>
    <string name="dealer_loginButton">dealer_loginButton</string>
    <string name="dealer_forgotpassword">dealer_forgotpassword</string>
    <string name="dealer_signup">dealer_signup</string>
    <string name="details_activity">Car Details</string>


    <string name="Name">Name</string>
    <string name="State">State</string>
    <string name="City">City</string>
    <string name="Mobileno">Mobile No</string>
    <string name="Email">Email Id</string>
    <string name="Pincode">Pincode</string>


    <string name="Email_FP">ENTER YOUR EMAIL</string>
    <string name="Enter_recived_otp">ENTER  YOUR MOBILE NUMBER</string>

    <string name="Dealerid">DEALER ID</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_message">Authenticating your credentials..Please wait..</string>

    <string name="forgot_password_message">Getting your password..Please wait..</string>

    <string name="sign_up_message">Registering you to our database..Please wait..</string>


    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer Close</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="activities">Activities</string>

    <!--  Navigation View String Values  -->
    <string name="dash_board">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="my_stock">MY Stock</string>
    <string name="Addcar">Add Car</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Reports">Reports</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="logout">Log out</string>


    <string name="share">Share App</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate App</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_usdoc">
Carsusb.com is one of India\'s leading online auto marketplace for dealers by providing buyers and sellers a structured platform for transacting in used vehicles. \nOur vision is to expand our offerings across India by forming a strong network of dealers which helps them manage their business operations.
What makes Carsusb.com unique are its offerings and world class technology. Some of the unique features include market place for dealers to add,\n view stock and buy cars from different companies and search desired cars at one go. Additionally, we also provide information related to the automobile industry and the latest automotive news. Our expert views and reviews of exciting upcoming models in the market guide and help dealers update on future business.
We\'re proud of our sincere and continuous efforts to help dealers excel in their businessin India. So whether you\'re a new or existing dealer we hope you\'ll find what you\'re looking for.
Investors and shareholders\n
We are open to business proposal from investors please do contact us for investing in breakthrough technology company.
Our ambition and energy, together we can create great company.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="tandc">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="tandc_doc"></string>

    <string name="Privacy_Policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policydoc">Carsusb.com - Privacy Policy\n\n
This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended
provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology
Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or
digital signatures.\n\n
This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website to the exclusion of any third party websites. The Website may
provide links to other sites which it believes may be of interest to the users of the Website. We do not guarantee
the privacy standards of those sites to which it links or be responsible for the contents of sites other than this
one, and this Privacy policy is not intended to be applicable to any linked, third party site.\n\n

Information you provide\n\n
As a Registered User, we ask you for Registration Data (such as your name, company name, phone nos., email
address, postal address, PAN, etc.) which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. You can decline to
submit personal information to any of our services, in which case the Website may not be able to provide any or
all services to you.\n\n
\n●Cookies: When you visit the Website, we send one or more cookies, a small file containing a string of
characters to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of
our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people use the Website, we
also uses cookies in for advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads
across the web.\n\n
\n●Log information: When you access the Website, our servers automatically record information that your
browser sends whenever you visit a Website. These server logs may include information such as your web
request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and
one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Also, in order to protect you from fraud,
phishing, and other misconduct, we may collect information about your interaction with our servers. Any
such information we collect will only be used to detect and prevent fraud or other misconduct.\n\n
\n●User communications: When you send email or other communications to the Website, we may retain
those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our
services.\n\n
\n●Affiliated sites: We may offer some of our services in connection with other websites. If necessary, the
information that you provide us might be shared with such websites in order to facilitate the objectives of
the Website. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and you are required to read their
privacy policies and shall be bound by the terms of use of such websites. We shall not be liable for any
policies and practices of such websites.\n\n
\n●Email Addresses If you provide us your email address, we may email you about our website or our
services, or to inquire about your experience using our website or sites operated by others. From time to
time, we\'ll also send you emails that may include automotive information; special promotions and other
commercial offers that we think may be of interest to you. Though we hope you\'ll find these
communications informative and useful, if you don\'t, you can always unsubscribe by following the simple
instructions included in each email.\n\n
\n●Links: The Website may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have
been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content
and advertising.\n\n

We only process personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the
supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:\n
\n●Providing our services to Users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
        \n
\n●Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;\n
\n●Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and\n\n
\n●Developing new services.\n\n
Information sharing​
​
we only share personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:
\n●We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the
number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a
particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.\n\n
\n●We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or
persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties
agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy
and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.\n\n
\n●We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably
necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request,
(b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect,
prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to
the rights, property or safety of the Website, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.\n\n
\n●In the event that the business of this Website and the customer data connected with it is merged, sold,
assigned or transferred, in which case we would require the buyer, assignee or transferee to treat personal
data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Information security​\n\n
​
Information gathered on the Website is stored within Carsusb.com controlled servers (or servers hosted on our
behalf) that are in a protected environment. We take appropriate security measures to protect against
unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal
reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical
security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. However,
no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers or
databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won\'t be intercepted while being transmitted to us
over the Internet. Although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not
expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.​\n\n
​
Accessing and updating personal information ​\n\n
​
when you use the Website, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information
and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise
required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask Users to identify themselves and the
information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may
decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical
effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise
required. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete personal information.​\n\n
​
Changes to this Privacy Policy​\n\n
​
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on
this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain
services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). By visiting and using Carsusb.com, you agree that your
visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Statement and our User Agreement.\n\n
 Agreement to Privacy Policy\n\n
Your use of this site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of the Carsusb.com Privacy Policy and your
continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you
do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.\n\n
Third Parties ​\n\n
This document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your
information to others whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our sites or other sites throughout the
internet or any other mode, and due to this act if any kind of liability occurs than the same shall be payable by
you and you shall be responsible for that.
\n\n
Communication​\n\n
You agree that we can and may communicate with you via phone calls, SMS, E-Mails and/or any other method
&amp; we will not be liable to you and/or any other authority for such an act. If your number is registered with any Do
Not Call (DNC) and/or Do Not Disturb (DND) service you hereby authorize us to communicate with you via
telephone calls, SMS, E-Mails and/or any other method and will not in any case hold us liable for any
communication in this regard.\n\n


</string>


    <string name="tc">Carsusb.com\t\t\t\t\t\tUser Agreement\n

This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended
provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology
Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or
digital signatures.\n
Welcome to www.Carsusb.com. If you continue to browse and use the Website / App (hereinafter, collectively
referred to as "Website") you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions
of use, including any future amendments (“Terms of Use”), which together with our Privacy Policy govern our
relationship with you in relation to this Website (“Agreement”).​\n\n
​
GENERAL\n
●For the purpose of the User Agreement, Registered User / and wherever the context so require \'You\' shall
mean any natural or legal person who has agreed to become a member of the Website by providing
Registration Data (as defined hereinafter) while registering on the Website using the computer systems of
the Website and accepted this electronic version / electronic record of the User Agreement and has
allocated himself a unique identification user name ("User ID" and "Password").\n
As a new Registered User, this User Agreement shall be effective and binding upon your \'acceptance\'.
\'Acceptance\' shall mean your affirmative action in clicking on \'check box\' and on the \'continue button\' as
provided on the registration page. If you do not agree or are not willing to be bound by the terms and
conditions of this User Agreement, please do not click on the "check box" and on the "Continue" button and
do not seek to obtain access to or otherwise use the Website.\n\n
●You may not modify copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create
derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products or services obtained from the
Website.\n\n
●As a condition of your use of the “Website”, you pledge that you will not use the site for any purpose that is
unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You may not use the Website in any manner
which could damage, disable, overburden, impair, or interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of
the Website. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not
intentionally made available or provided for through the Website. You agree, and are hereby put on notice,
that you are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Website any unlawful, threatening,
libellous, defamatory, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material or any other material that could give
rise to any civil or criminal liability under law. You are solely responsible for the content of any comments
you make.\n\n
●AMENDMENTS\n
Carsusb Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “Carsusb”) may amend this User Agreement and/or the Carsusb
Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on the Website. All updates and amendments shall be
notified to you via Carsusb website. The revised version will be effective at the time carsusb posts it on the
website.  You are advised to regularly check for any amendments or updates to the terms and conditions
contained in this User Agreement and in the Carsusb.com Privacy Policy.\n\n
●MEMBERSHIP ELIGIBILITY\n
Use of the Website is available only to persons who can form legally binding contracts under Indian Contract
Act, 1872. Persons who are "incompetent to contract" within the meaning of the Indian Contract Act, 1872
including minors, un-discharged insolvents etc. are not eligible to use the Website. If you are a minor i.e. under
the age of 18 years, you shall not register as a member of the Website. Carsusb reserves the right to terminate
your membership and refuse to provide you with access to the Website if it is brought to Carsusb notice or if it is
discovered that you are under the age of 18 years.\n\n
●BUSINESS ENTITY REGISTRATION\n
If you are registering as a business entity, you represent that you are duly authorised by the business entity to
accept this User Agreement and you have the authority to bind that business entity to this User Agreement and
Privacy Policy.\n\n
●YOUR ACCOUNT AND REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS\n\n
​
If you use the Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your User ID and
Password and for restricting access to your computer, computer system and computer network, and you
are responsible for all activities that occur under your User ID and Password. In addition, you agree to
provide true, accurate, current and complete information into the Website.\n

●ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATION\n
When you use the Website, You agree and understand that you are communicating with Carsusb through
electronic records and you consent to receive communications via electronic records from Carsusb periodically
and as and when required. Carsusb will communicate with you by email or by an electronic record on the
Carsusb.com website which will be deemed adequate service of notice / electronic record.\n\n
●USE OF THE WEBSITE​\n
You understand and agree that Carsusb and the Website merely provide services to its Registered Users.
All items advertised / listed and the contents therein are advertised and listed are third party user
generated contents. Carsusb neither initiates the transmission nor selects the sender and receiver of the
transmission nor selects nor modify the information contained in the transmission. Carsusb has no control
over the third party user generated contents.\n ​
​
You agree, undertake and confirm that your use of the Website shall be strictly governed by the following
binding principles: "Your Information" is defined as any information you provide on the Website. You are
solely responsible for Your Information, and we act only as a passive conduit for your online distribution
and publication of Your Information\n\n
○Your Information (or any items listed) :\n
■shall not be false, inaccurate or misleading;\n
■shall not be fraudulent or involve the sale of counterfeit or stolen items;\n
■shall not infringe any third party\'s intellectual property, trade secret or other proprietary rights or
rights of publicity or privacy;\n
■shall not, directly or indirectly, offer, attempt to offer, trade or attempt to trade in any item, the
dealing of which is prohibited or restricted in any manner under the provisions of any applicable
law, rule, regulation or guideline for the time being in force. Without prejudice to the generality of
the above, Carsusb does not permit transactions in the following items including but not limited to
categories as stated in this document.\n
■shall not contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, easter eggs or other
computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, diminish value of,
surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information\n
■shall not create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs or
other suppliers; and
Solely to enable Carsusb to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you
might have in Your Information, you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable,
royalty-free, sub-licensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights
(but no other rights) you have in Your Information, in any media now known or not currently known, with respect
to Your Information. Carsusb will only use Your Information in accordance with this Agreement. In the event that
any transaction, attempted transaction or information relating to any item, good or service which is in violation
of this User Agreement or applicable law comes to your knowledge, you shall take all steps to inform Carsusb
of the same. You may contact Carsusb from Contact Us ​\n\n
​
You shall comply with all applicable Domestic laws, rules and regulations (including the provisions of any
applicable Exchange Control Laws or Regulations in Force) and International Laws, Foreign Exchange Laws,
Statutes, Ordinances and Regulations (including, but not limited to Sales Tax/ VAT, Income Tax, Octroi, Service
Tax, Central Excise, Custom Duty, Local Levies) regarding your use of the Website. You shall not engage in any
transaction in an item or service, which is prohibited by the provisions of any applicable law including
exchange control laws or regulations for the time being in force. ​\n\n
​
From time to time, you shall be responsible for providing information relating to the items or services. In this
connection, you undertake that all such information shall be accurate in all respects. You shall not exaggerate
or over emphasize the attributes of such items or services so as to mislead other Users in any manner. ​\n\n
​
You shall not attempt to or circumvent or manipulate our Fee structure, the billing process or Fees owed to
Carsusb.\n\n
PLATFORM FOR COMMUNICATION​\n\n
​
Carsusb is not and cannot be a party to or control in any manner any interaction between two Users of the\n
Website or any other third party. Consequently:\n
○Carsusb does not make any representation or Warranty as to the attributes (such as quality, worth,
marketability, etc.) of the items or services on the Website. Carsusb accepts no liability for any errors
or omissions, whether on behalf of itself or third parties.\n
○Carsusb does not make any representation or warranty as to the attributes (such as legal title,
creditworthiness, identity, etc.) of any information on the Website. You are advised to independently
verify the bona fides of any particular User that you choose to deal with on the Website and use your
best judgment in that behalf.\n
○Carsusb is only providing a platform for communication and it is agreed that the contract for sale of
any of the products or services shall be a strictly bipartite contract between the two parties. At no time
shall any right, title or interest over the items vest with Carsusb nor shall Carsusb have any obligations
or liabilities in respect of such contract. Carsusb is not responsible for unsatisfactory or delayed
performance of services or damages or delays as a result of items which are out of stock, back
ordered or otherwise unavailable. At no time shall any right, title or interest over the items vest with
Carsusb nor shall Carsusb have any obligations or liabilities in respect of such contract. Carsusb is
not responsible for unsatisfactory or delayed performance of services or damages or delays.\n\n
●BREACH​\n
Without limiting other remedies, Carsusb may limit your activity, immediately temporarily/indefinitely
suspend or terminate your membership, and/or refuse to provide you with access to the Website in the
event, but not limited to:
        \n
○If you breach the User Agreement or the documents, agreements rules, policies, terms and conditions
these incorporate by reference;\n
○If Carsusb is unable to verify or authenticate any information you provide; or\n
○If it is believed that your actions may cause legal liability for you, other Users or Carsusb.\n
○Carsusb may at any time at its sole discretion reinstate suspended Users. A User that has been
indefinitely suspended may not register or attempt to register with Carsusb or use the Website in any
manner whatsoever until such time that such User is reinstated by Carsusb. Notwithstanding the
foregoing, if you breach the User Agreement or the documents it incorporates by reference, Carsusb
reserves the right to recover any amounts due and owing by you to Carsusb and to take strict legal
action including but not limited to a referral to the appropriate police or other authorities for initiating
criminal or other proceedings against you.\n
●NO WARRANTY​\n\n
Carsusb and its suppliers, affiliates and service providers provide the Website "as is" and without any
Warranty or condition, express, implied or statutory and specifically disclaim any implied Warranties of title,
merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. You expressly agree that your use of
the Website is at your risk.\n\n

●LIMITATION OF LIABILITY ​\n\n
In no event shall Carsusb or its suppliers, affiliates and service providers be liable for any direct, indirect,
incidental, special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages
for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses arising out of or in connection with the
Website, its services or this agreement (however arising, including negligence).
Carsusb  its associates, affiliates and service providers and technology partners make no representations or
Warranties about the accuracy, reliability, completeness, and/or timeliness of any content, information, software,
text, graphics, links or communications provided on or through the use of the Website or that the operation of
the Website or will be error free and/or uninterrupted. Consequently, Carsusb assumes no liability whatsoever
for any monetary or other damage suffered by you on account of:\n
○The delay, failure, interruption, or corruption of any data or other information transmitted in connection
with use of the Website.\n
○Any interruption or errors in the operation of the Website. You expressly understand and agree that
Carsusb  shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary
damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other
intangible losses (even if Carsusb has been advised of the possibility of such damages).\n
○The content, accuracy and reliability of the material provided by the other users or any other
individual.\n\n
●PROPRIETARY RIGHTS\n
The information contained in this Website including all images, illustrations, designs, photographs, video clips,
writings and other materials that appear herein are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress or other intellectual
property owned, controlled, or licensed (all of which, collectively, “Contents”) by the Website or its subsidiaries
and affiliates or are the property of their respective owners. The name “Carsusb.com” and its logos are
trademarks of the Website.\n\n

●REPRESENTATIONS &amp; WARRANTIES OF CARSUSB\n\n
The Website and/or its respective suppliers, affiliates, associates, representatives make no representations
about the suitability, reliability, availability, timeliness and accuracy of the information, products and services
contained on the Website for any purpose. All such information, products offered, services offered etc. are
provided on an "as is where is" basis without warranty of any kind. Website and/or its respective suppliers,
associates, affiliates hereby disclaim all warranties and conditions with regard to the information, products,
services, including all implied warranties and conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title
and non-infringement. Nor do they guarantee that this information will be error free or continuously available, or
that the service will be free of viruses or other harmful components. The information generated by the Website
is believed to be accurate, but the Website and its suppliers do not warrant or guarantee such accuracy. The
Website and its suppliers do not authorize the use of such information for any purpose other than your personal
use, and prohibit to the maximum extent allowable the resale, redistribution, and use of this information for
commercial purposes.​\n
In no event shall the Website be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, consequential
damages or any damages whatsoever including without limitation, damages for loss of use arising out of or in
any way connected with the use or performance of the Website, with the delay or inability to use the Website or
related services, the provision or failure to provide services, or for any information, products, services and
related graphics obtained through the Website, or otherwise arising out of the use of the Website, whether
based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, even if the Website or any of its
suppliers/affiliates has been advised of the possibility of damages. If you are dissatisfied with any portion of the
Website or with any of these terms of use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Website.​
The Website shall not be responsible for, and does not guarantee the performance of, any goods or services
purchased through the Website\n\n
●REPRESENTATIONS &amp; WARRANTIES OF USER\n
You shall not upload from, post or transmit or distribute or otherwise publish through the Site any materials
which  restrict any other user from using the Site and /or  are unlawful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, vulgar,
offensive, pornographic, or indecent and /or constitute or contain false or misleading indications of origin or
statements of fact.  You further represents and warrants Carsusb that all the information provided by you about
yourself are true and accurate; and you shall be responsible for all actions taken by you or by any other
individual through your ID to whom you have given authorization to use.\n\n
●COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARKS\n
Unless otherwise stated, copyright and all intellectual property rights in all material presented on the site
including but not limited to text, graphics, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data
compilations, and software, trademarks and logos appearing on the site are the property of the Carsusb, its
parent, affiliates and associates and are protected under applicable Indian and international laws. You agree
not to use any trademark or logo or other proprietary information of the Carsusb.\n\n
●COMMUNICATION\n\n
You agree that Carsusb can and may communicate with you via phone calls, SMS, E-Mails and/or any other
method &amp; Carsusb will not be liable to you and/or any other authority for such an act. If your number is
registered with any Do Not Call (DNC) and/or Do Not Disturb (DND) service you hereby authorize Carsusb to
communicate with you via telephone calls, SMS, E-Mails and/or any other method and You will not in any case
hold Carsusb liable for any communication in this regard.\n\n

●INDEMNITY ​\n
You shall indemnify and hold harmless Carsusb and (as applicable) Carsusb parent, subsidiaries,
affiliates, third-parties and their respective officers, directors, agents, employees, suppliers, service
partners, agents and consultants from any claim or demand, or actions including reasonable attorneys\'
fees, made by any third party or penalty imposed due to or arising out of your breach of this Agreement, or
the documents they incorporates by reference, or your violation of any law, rules or regulations or the
rights of a third party.\n\n

●RELATIONSHIP, NOTICE AND SEVERABILITY ​\n
none of the provisions of the User Agreement shall be deemed to constitute a partnership or agency
between you and Carsusb and you shall have no authority to bind Carsusb in any manner whatsoever.
Except as explicitly stated otherwise, any notices shall be given by registered postal mail on behalf of  Carsusb
Attn: Legal Department,  Carsusb  Pvt. Ltd, ( 4M-504 , OUTER RING ROAD , KAMANAHALLI, KALYANAGAR-
BANGALORE-560043  or to the email address you provide to us during the registration process (in your case).
Notice shall be deemed given 24 hours after email is sent, unless the sending party is notified that the email
address is invalid. Alternatively, we may give you notice by certified mail, postage prepaid and return receipt
requested, to the address provided to us during the registration process. In such case, notice shall be deemed
given 3 days after the date of mailing. ​\n\n
​
If any clause of the User Agreement shall be deemed invalid, void or for any reason unenforceable, such
clause shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining clauses
of the User Agreement.\n\n
●ARBITRATION​\n
If any dispute arises between you and Carsusb during your use of the Website or thereafter, in connection
with the validity, interpretation, implementation or alleged breach of any provision of the User Agreement
and Seller Terms and Conditions or the documents they incorporates by reference, the dispute shall be
referred to a sole Arbitrator who shall be an independent and neutral third party identified by Carsusb. The
place of arbitration shall be Bangalore. The Arbitration &amp; Conciliation Act, 1996, shall govern the
arbitration proceedings. The arbitration proceedings shall be in the English language and each party shall
pay their own costs.\n\n
●GOVERNING LAW​\n
The User Agreement Terms and Conditions or the documents they incorporates by reference shall be
governed and construed in accordance with the laws of India\n\n
●ENTIRE AGREEMENT\n
Unless otherwise specified herein, the Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the User and the
Website and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic,
oral or written, between the User and the Website. A printed version of this Agreement and of any notice given
in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this
Agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records
originally generated and maintained in printed form. \n\n\n</string>


    <string name="AUCTION">Auction</string>
    <string name="FINANCE">Finance</string>
    <string name="MARKET">Market</string>
    <string name="REQUIREMENTS">Requirements</string>
    <string name="LEADS">Leads</string>
    <string name="search_car">Advance Search</string>
    <string name="LOANS">Loans</string>
    <string name="INSURANCE">Insurance</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!--  Add Car String Values -->
    <string name="car_images">Upload Car Images</string>
    <string name="insurance_upload">Upload Insurance</string>
    <string name="rc_book_upload">Upload RC Book </string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="sl_notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="reg_no">Reg No.</string>
    <string name="make">Make</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="varient">Variant</string>
    <string name="fuel">Fuel</string>
    <string name="colour">Color</string>
    <string name="kms">Kms</string>
    <string name="transmission">Transmission</string>
    <string name="owners">Owners</string>
    <string name="insurance">Insurance</string>
    <string name="expiry_date">Expiry Date</string>
    <string name="expected_price">Expected Price</string>

    <!--searchcar_scrollview-->
    <string name="search_car_scrolview">searchcar_scrollview</string>

    <string name="add_more">Add More</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="bulk_upload">BULK UPLOAD</string>

    <!--car documents-->
    <string name="car_doc">CAR</string>
    <string name="rc_doc">RC BOOK</string>
    <string name="insurance_doc">INSURANCE </string>

    <!--  Search Car String Values -->
    <string name="search_car_carsearch">CAR SEARCH:</string>
    <string name="search_car_State">State</string>
    <string name="search_car_City">City</string>
    <string name="search_car_Make">Make</string>
    <string name="search_car_CarPrice">Car Price</string>
    <string name="search_car_Fuel">Fuel</string>
    <string name="search_car_KMS">Kms</string>
    <string name="search_car_Age">Age</string>

    <string name="search_car_Transmission">Transmission</string>
    <string name="search_car_Model">Model</string>
    <string name="search_car_Variant">Variant</string>
    <string name="search_car_mobile">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="search_car_regnumber">Reg Number</string>
    <string name="search_car_Color">Colour</string>

    <string name="search_car_submit">Submit</string>

    <!--  car specification Details String Values -->
    <string name="cardetail_Gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="car_detail">Car Details</string>

    <!--  Dashboard Fragment Values -->
    <string name="car_report">Car Report Tracking Details</string>
    <string name="current_month">Current Month</string>
    <string name="current_inventory">Total Stock</string>
    <string name="sold_status">Sold Status</string>
    <string name="total_purchase">Total stock</string>

    <string name="total_stock">Total Sold</string>
    <string name="total_sold">Total Sold</string>

    <string name="top_vehicles">My Stock</string>

    <!--url link of CARUSB-->
    <string name="link"><a href="http://www.carsusb.com" rel="nofollow">@ 2016 www.carsusb.com</a></string>
    <string name="reg_email_id">Please enter your  mobile number to recieve password.</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Please Enter your Mobile no to get OTP</string>
    <string name="url">\@2016 www.carsusb.com</string>
    <string name="select_image">Select Image</string>
    <string name="share_text">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=sample.com.carusb</string>
    <string name="share_text_choose_option">Share app Using</string>


    <!--  Myprofile details -->
    <string name="my_Name">Name</string>
    <string name="my_state">State</string>
    <string name="My_City">City</string>
    <string name="my_Address">Address</string>
    <string name="my_Pincode">Pincode</string>
    <string name="My_MobileNo">Mobile No</string>
    <string name="my_Phone">Phone </string>
    <string name="my_Email">Email</string>
    <string name="My_Submit">Submit</string>

    <!--  Myprofile details -->
    <string name="contact_address">Cars USB Headquarters:\n  CARSUSB Pvt Ltd\n#75,Hebbal,Bangalore-560024\n E-mail:\tinfo@carsusb.com\n

Tech Support:\tsupport@carsusb.com\n

Contact:\t+91-9019834355\n</string>
    <string name="sl_no">Sl_No</string>
    <string name="search_menu">Search</string>
    <string name="mobile"> Enter Your Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="sold">Sold</string>
    <string name="shortlist">Shortlist</string>
    <!--add car-->

    <string-array name="addcar_select_variant">
        <item>333</item>
        <item>444</item>
        <item>555</item>
        <item>666</item>
        <item>999</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="addcar_select_make">
        <item>Astin Martin</item>
        <item>Astin</item>
        <item>Bentley</item>
        <item>Bmw</item>
        <item>Audi</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addcar_select_model">
        <item>A1</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_year">
        <item>2017</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2015</item>
        <item>2014</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2011</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2009</item>
        <item>2008</item>
        <item>2007</item>
        <item>2006</item>
        <item>2005</item>
        <item>2004</item>
        <item>2003</item>
        <item>2002</item>
        <item>2001</item>
        <item>2000</item>
        <item>1999</item>
        <item>1998</item>
        <item>1997</item>
        <item>1996</item>
        <item>1995</item>
        <item>1994</item>
        <item>1993</item>
        <item>1992</item>
        <item>1991</item>
        <item>1990</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_color">
        <item>Beige</item>
        <item>Black</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Bronze</item>
        <item>Brown</item>
        <item>Gold</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Grey</item>
        <item>Maroon</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Purple</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Silver</item>
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="search_select_fuel">
        <item>Petrol</item>
        <item>Diesel</item>
        <item>LPG</item>
        <item>CNG</item>
        <item>Electric</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_transmission">
        <item>Manual</item>
        <item>Automatic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_owners">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addcar_select_expected_price">
        <item>0-200000</item>
        <item>200000-500000</item>
        <item>500000-1000000</item>
        <item>1000000-1500000</item>
        <item>1500000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_kms">
        <item>0-5000</item>
        <item>5000-15000</item>
        <item>15000 - 30000</item>
        <item>30000 - 50000</item>
        <item>50000-100000</item>
        <item>100000+</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_age">
        <item>0 - 2 years</item>
        <item>2 - 4 years</item>
        <item>4 - 6 years</item>
        <item>6 - 8 years</item>
        <item>8 +years</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addcar_select_insurance">
        <item>COMP</item>
        <item>T/P</item>
        <item>NA</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addcar_select_fuel">
        <item>Petrol</item>
        <item>Diesel</item>
        <item>LPG</item>
        <item>CNG</item>
        <item>Electric</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="india_states">
        <item>ANDAMAN AND NICOBAR</item>
        <item>ANDHRA PRADESH</item>
        <item>ARUNACHAL PRADESH</item>
        <item>ASSAM</item>
        <item>BIHAR</item>
        <item>CHANDIGARH</item>
        <item>CHHATTISGARH</item>
        <item>DADRA AND NAGAR HAVELI</item>
        <item>DAMAN AND DIU</item>
        <item>DELHI</item>
        <item>GOA</item>
        <item>GUJARAT</item>
        <item>HARYANA</item>
        <item>HIMACHAL PRADESH</item>
        <item>JAMMU AND KASHMIR</item>
        <item>JHARKHAND</item>
        <item>KARNATAKA</item>
        <item>KERALA</item>
        <item>LAKSHADWEEP</item>
        <item>MADHYA PRADESH</item>
        <item>MAHARASHTRA</item>
        <item>MANIPUR</item>
        <item>MEGHALAYA</item>
        <item>MIZORAM</item>
        <item>NAGALAND</item>
        <item>ORISSA</item>
        <item>PONDICHERRY</item>
        <item>PUNJAB</item>
        <item>RAJASTHAN</item>
        <item>SIKKIM</item>
        <item>TAMIL NADU</item>
        <item>TRIPURA</item>
        <item>UTTARANCHAL</item>
        <item>UTTAR PRADESH</item>
        <item>WEST BENGAL</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="india_top_places">
        <item>Agartala</item>
        <item>Agra</item>
        <item>Agumbe</item>
        <item>Ahmedabad</item>
        <item>Aizawl</item>
        <item>Ajmer</item>
        <item>Alappuzha Beach</item>
        <item>Allahabad</item>
        <item>Alleppey</item>
        <item>Almora</item>
        <item>Amarnath</item>
        <item>Amritsar</item>
        <item>Anantagir</item>
        <item>Andaman and Nicobar Islands</item>
        <item>Araku valley</item>
        <item>Aurangabad</item>
        <item>Ayodhya</item>
        <item>Badrinath</item>
        <item>Bangalore</item>
        <item>Baroda</item>
        <item>Bastar</item>
        <item>Bhagalpur</item>
        <item>Bhilai</item>
        <item>Bhimtal</item>
        <item>Bhopal</item>
        <item>Bhubaneswar</item>
        <item>Bhuj</item>
        <item>Bidar</item>
        <item>Bilaspur</item>
        <item>Bodh Gaya</item>
        <item>Calicut</item>
        <item>Chail</item>
        <item>Chamba</item>
        <item>Chandigarh</item>
        <item>Chennai</item>
        <item>Chennai Beaches</item>
        <item>Cherai</item>
        <item>Cherrapunji</item>
        <item>Chidambaram</item>
        <item>Chikhaldara Hills</item>
        <item>Chopta</item>
        <item>Coimbatore</item>
        <item>Coonoor</item>
        <item>Coorg</item>
        <item>Corbett National Park</item>
        <item>Cotigao Wild Life Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Cuttack</item>
        <item>Dadra and Nagar Haveli</item>
        <item>Dalhousie</item>
        <item>Daman and Diu</item>
        <item>Darjeeling</item>
        <item>Dehradun</item>
        <item>Delhi</item>
        <item>Devikulam</item>
        <item>Dhanaulti</item>
        <item>Dharamashala</item>
        <item>Dindigul</item>
        <item>Dudhwa National Park</item>
        <item>Dwaraka</item>
        <item>Faridabad</item>
        <item>Gandhinagar</item>
        <item>Gangotri</item>
        <item>Gangtok</item>
        <item>Gir Wildlife Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Goa</item>
        <item>Great Himalayan National Park</item>
        <item>Gulmarg</item>
        <item>Gurgaon</item>
        <item>Guruvayoor</item>
        <item>Guwahati</item>
        <item>Gwalior</item>
        <item>Hampi</item>
        <item>Haridwar</item>
        <item>Hogenakkal</item>
        <item>Horsley Hills</item>
        <item>Hyderabad</item>
        <item>Idukki</item>
        <item>Imphal</item>
        <item>Indore</item>
        <item>Itangar</item>
        <item>Jabalpur</item>
        <item>Jaipur</item>
        <item>Jaisalmer</item>
        <item>Jalandhar</item>
        <item>Jammu</item>
        <item>Jamshedpur</item>
        <item>Jodhpur</item>
        <item>Kanchipuram</item>
        <item>Kanha National Park</item>
        <item>Kanpur</item>
        <item>Kanyakumari</item>
        <item>Kargil</item>
        <item>Karwar</item>
        <item>Kausani</item>
        <item>Kedarnath</item>
        <item>Keoladeoghana National Park</item>
        <item>Khajuraho</item>
        <item>Kochi</item>
        <item>Kodaikanal</item>
        <item>Kolkata</item>
        <item>Kollam</item>
        <item>Konark</item>
        <item>Kotagiri</item>
        <item>Kottakkal and Ayurveda</item>
        <item>Kovalam</item>
        <item>Kovalam and Ayurveda</item>
        <item>Kudremukh</item>
        <item>Kullu</item>
        <item>Kumaon</item>
        <item>Kumarakom</item>
        <item>Kumarakom and Ayurveda</item>
        <item>Kumarakom Bird Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Kurukshetra</item>
        <item>Lakshadweep</item>
        <item>Lucknow</item>
        <item>Ludhiana</item>
        <item>Madurai</item>
        <item>Mahabalipuram</item>
        <item>Malpe Beach</item>
        <item>Manas National Park</item>
        <item>Mangalore</item>
        <item>Maravanthe Beach</item>
        <item>Margoa</item>
        <item>Mount Abu</item>
        <item>Mumbai</item>
        <item>Munnar</item>
        <item>Mussoorie</item>
        <item>Mysore</item>
        <item>Nahsik</item>
        <item>Nalanda</item>
        <item>Nanda Devi National Park</item>
        <item>Nandi Hills</item>
        <item>Netravali Wild Life Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Ooty</item>
        <item>Orchha</item>
        <item>Pahalgam</item>
        <item>Palakkad</item>
        <item>Panchgani</item>
        <item>Patna</item>
        <item>Patnitop</item>
        <item>Pattadakkal</item>
        <item>Periyar Wildlife Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Pithoragarh</item>
        <item>Pondicherry</item>
        <item>Pune</item>
        <item>Puri</item>
        <item>Pushkar</item>
        <item>Raipur</item>
        <item>Rajaji National Park</item>
        <item>Rajgir</item>
        <item>Rameshwaram</item>
        <item>Ranchi</item>
        <item>Ranganthittu Bird Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Ranikhet</item>
        <item>Ranthambore</item>
        <item>Rishikesh</item>
        <item>Rourkela</item>
        <item>Sanchi</item>
        <item>Saputara</item>
        <item>Sariska Wildlife Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Shillong</item>
        <item>Shimla</item>
        <item>Sohna_Hills</item>
        <item>Srinagar</item>
        <item>Sunderbans</item>
        <item>Surat</item>
        <item>Tezpur</item>
        <item>Thanjavur</item>
        <item>Thiruvananthapuram</item>
        <item>Thrissur</item>
        <item>Tirunelveli</item>
        <item>Tirupati</item>
        <item>Trichy</item>
        <item>Udaipur</item>
        <item>Ujjain</item>
        <item>Vaishali</item>
        <item>Valley of Flowers</item>
        <item>Varanasi</item>
        <item>Varkala and Ayurveda</item>
        <item>Vijayawada</item>
        <item>Vishakhapatnam</item>
        <item>Vrindhavan</item>
        <item>Warangal</item>
        <item>Wayanad</item>
        <item>Wayanad Wildlife Sanctuary</item>
        <item>Yercaud</item>
        <item>Zanskar</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
